President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of John M. Sayles, 1930-1950; 3; 4.67 cubic ft.
  - Association of Colleges and Universities, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albany Community War Chest aka Albany War Chest - Albany Victory War Chest, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrative (closing of class controversy), 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Air Raid Procedure, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Day Speech, 1942; 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Admissions, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adult Education Council, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Albany Home for Children, 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of NY Committee on Teacher Education - Speight, Harold, Executive Secretary, 1939-1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of NY - Five Year Plan Teacher Education, 1940; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Association of Teacher Colleges, 1939-1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Association of University Women, 1940-1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Council on Education, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1939-1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report - Milne Report, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report - Placement Bureau, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report - Placement Bureau, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Association of Colleges and Universitites of the State of NY - Albany Faculty Workshop, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Association of Secondary School Principals, 1938; 1945; 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Association of Teacher Colleges, 1940-1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Associated Academic Principals of NYS, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NYS Association of Faculties of Teacher Colleges and Normal Schools, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NY Association of Teachers College Faculties, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Athletics, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Audio - Visual Aids, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Aviation Workshops Study Conference on Education for the Air Age, 1942-1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - B - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1940-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Board of Regents (Organization Charts), 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Office of the President Board of Vistors, 1939-1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Brubacher Student Memorial Brubacher Bio, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Budget Matters, employee information, 1942-1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Budget, NYSCT, 1939-1944 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - [Teacher] Appointment Bureau, 1942-1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chemistry Department - Remodeling, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry Laboratory, 1942-1946 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Civil Service Annual Rating, 1947-1948; 1950 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Commencement, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commeres Department, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Report, 1941-1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Teacher Education, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Conference of Administrators, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cooper, Herman, 1939-1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cooper, Herman (Assistant Commissioner for Teacher Evaluation, 1939-1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cooper - Property, 1939-1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Test Service B.W Wood, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Council on Cooperative in Teacher Education, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Curriculum, 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Department of Civil Service, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Departmental Reports Milne High School, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Departmental Reports Dean's Office, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - E - Correspondence, 1940; 1944 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dormitory Authority - Correspondence + Minutes + By Laws, 1944-1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - English Department Report, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Education Policies Commission, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Executive Dean for Education, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Executive Dean for Teacher Education (SUNY), 1942-1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - F - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Faculty - Administration Council (Faculty Council), 1944-1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Appointments and Changes, 1939-1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Federal Aid, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Federal Housing, 1946; 1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Financial Reports - Losses, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fisk Roberts, 1946; 1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Office of the President Five Year Plan, 1939; 1946; 1947 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - French House, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Addresses Classes 1941-1940, 1941 September-1946 September (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - William M. French, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - G - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - James Gemmil, 1942-1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gideon Hawley & Milne Murals, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School - AU Departments, 1935-1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - H - Correspondence, 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hardy, Wm G., 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Hastings, Harry, 1941-1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hatfield, D. Elliot, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hickey, Dorothy, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Home Economics Department, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Housing Information, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hutchins, Ruth Art Department WPA, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - I - Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Individual Reports from Various Departments for Annual Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Institute of International Education, 1942-1947 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Institutution of Pacific Relations, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Interculture Relations, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Interculture Relations, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Intergroup Relations, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - J - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - K - Correspondence, 1933-1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - L - Correspondence, 1941-1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Lang, Varley Military, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Leaves of Absences, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Legation of Switzerland, Letter, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NYS Legislature, 1941-1946 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Letters from Almuni, etc (Centenial Celebration), 1944 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Library Committee - Report, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Library School, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - M - Correspondence, 1934-1947 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mathematics Department, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda File, 1929-1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Hillis Miller - Association Commissioner of Higher Education, 1945-1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Middle Statue Association, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Military Training, 1941-1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Milne High School, 1939-1946 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Montgomery Ward Scholorship, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - N - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Student Peronnel Committee - Elizabeth Morris - Educational Testing, 1934-1946 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - National Teacher Examinations, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New York State War Council (War Training Programs), 1942 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - New York Times "Test" on American History, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Camp - Life Camps, 1942-1945 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Milton G. Nelson - Dean, 1942-1947 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - National Education Association, 1939-1947 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - National Youth Administration, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Navy, 1942-1947 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Need for a State University, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - New York State Teacher's Association, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - New York State Teacher's Association, 1943-1947 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NYSCT - Misc, 1931-1947 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, ca. 1940 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - O - Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - P - Correspomdence, 1940-1947 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Placement Date, 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Plans for Downtown Campus, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Personal Notes of 1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Post War Education (Floor Plans and Room Space for Future Development), 1944 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Post War Education Facilities, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Physical Education, 1941-1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Placement Date, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Police Department, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - President's Report, 1938-1941 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - President's Report, 1941-1944 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Projection of the Five Year Plan for the Improvement of the Teacher's College, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaire, 1942-1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Religious Education, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Reports: American Association of Teacher's College, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Report of Department of Education, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Report of Examination of Income Accounts and Financial Records, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Projected Five Year Plan, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Residence Halls, NYSCT, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - S - Correspondence, 1936-1947 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sabol, Edward Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Schmidt, AW (Assistant Commission of Finance), 1936; 1940-1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Schmidt, AW, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Science and Geography Department, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Service Flag Dedication, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Signum Laudis, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Dr Dormal V, 1942-1942; 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Special Fund Estimate, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Stewart, Watt, Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - St. Mary's Park Veterans Housing, Dormitory, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Student Christian Association, 1939-1942 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Student Injuries During Class Rivalry, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Student Union, 1945-1949 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Summer Sessions, 1940-1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Survery of Critical Materials (Divisions of Standards and Purchase), 1942 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Syracuse Conference "Competence of Teacher Coverage Students", 1947 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - T - Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Teacher's College, 1940-1945 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Teacher - Placement - NYSCT Albany, 1949-1950; 1958 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Teacher Training, 1939-1940 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - U - Correspondence, 1941-1946 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - United States Office of Education, 1941-1946 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - U.S Army, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - University Club, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - V - Correspondence, 1941-1947 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - W - Correspondence, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - War Man Power Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - War Relief Control Board, War Finance Committee, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - War Service Oppurtunity, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Katherine Wheeling Retirement, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Walter Woodward - Correspondence Re Milne High School, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Workshop, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - George York - NYSCT Commerce Department, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Office of Milton Nelson Records, 1946-1951; 4; 0.80 cubic ft.
  Series is arranged in alphabetical order.
  The materials in this series cover this over two year period that Nelson was in the position of President of the college. Milton G. Nelson was acting President in the wake of John Sayles sudden illness in the winter of 1947. The materials include reports from the president, correspondence with faculty and staff, as well as some select materials from Nelsons time as Dean of the College.
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 1)
  - American Council on Education, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 3)
  - Board of Visitors, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1948-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 2)
  - Budget Director's Approval, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 5)
  - Campus student Teaching, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 7)
  - Committee Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 3)
  - Construction, Improvements, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 9)
  - Coorespondence W, 1947 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 10)
  - Curriculum and Graduate committee, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 11)
  - Department of Education report, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 12)
  - Department Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 13)
  - Executive Dean for Teachers Education, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 14)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 15)
  - Faculty Status, 1951 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 16)
  - Federal Security Agency, National Youth Administration, 1939 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 17)
  - Freshman Addresses, 1952 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 18)
  - Gemmel, Professor James, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 19)
  - Heyden, Velma, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 20)
  - Housing (Dormitories and Cafeteria), 1946-1950 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 21)
  - Housing (Dormitories and Cafeteria), 1946-1950 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 22)
  - Housing (Dormitories and Cafeteria), 1946-1950 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 1)
  - Huyck Preserve, 1945 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 2)
  - Inter-Group Council, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 3)
  - Invoices, H, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 4)
  - Invoices, I, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 5)
  - Invoices, L, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 6)
  - Men's Athletic Association Manual, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 7)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 8)
  - Misc. J-K Invoices, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 9)
  - Physical Education Report, 1947-1948 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 10)
  - Rhodes, Scholarship Trust, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 11)
  - Sabol, Edward Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 12)
  - State Architect, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 13)
  - St. Mary's Park- Emergency Veterans Housing Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 14)
  - Student Medical Insurance, 1947-1948 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 15)
  - Student Union, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 16)
  - Survey of Fiscal Affairs for the State College, 1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 17)
  - Teacher Placement Brueau, 1948 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 18)
  - Vaccines, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 19)
- Office of Evan R. Collins Records, 1949-1969; 5; 14.92 cubic ft.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Researchers may access items in this series, yet often files must be reviewed by an archivist to ensure compliance with New York State Public Records laws. Please consult an archivist for more information.
  This series contains materials related to the presidency of Evan Revere Collins, who held the position from 1949-1969. The origin of these materials trace to both Evan Collins himself, as well as the Presidential office from this time. These cover the important changes occurring on the campus at this time, including expansion of the downtown dormitories at Alumni Quadrangle, as well as the construction of the Uptown Campus, and the change of the New York State College for Teachers, into a University Center. Specific materials in the series include reports from individual departments, correspondence with staff and contractors, and annual reports form Collins, as well as those sent to the office of the president such as the Milne School annual report. There are some materials that date to after Collins presidency, and were most likely part of the records keeping of the Office of the President after the move to the uptown campus.
  - A, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Program Approvals and Registrations, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Dean, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Common Academic Standing, 1952-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National Commission on Accreditation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administration, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Organization of the University l, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Organization of the University ll, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Admissions, 1959-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Admissions, 1959-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Common Admissions, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Admission Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Admission Committee Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Admission Information, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Board Budget Materials, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Albany Guidance, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Albany Home for Children, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Albany Institute of History and Art, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Albany, Role in College Study", Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Association - Correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Albany YMCA, 1956-1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Association, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Association - Benevolent Association Inc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Association - General and Financial Material - Council, Constitution and By-laws, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Association - Meetings, Reports and Minutes, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Council, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Day, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Residence Halls, 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - American Association of College for Teacher Education, 1954 December 5-1954 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - American Association of College for Teacher Education, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - American Association of College Teachers - Cleogo and Indianapolis Meeting, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American Association of College Teacher Education and Virility Committee, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AACTE - Evaluation Report, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - AACTE Visitation, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - AACTE Worksheets, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - AAUP, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - American Council on Education, 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - American Studies Program - Planting Fields Foundation, 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Department of Ancient Languages, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Appointments Approved, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Appointment Book, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Appointment Book, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ant Dept., Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Collection of Arts and Sciences, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Collection of Arts and Sciences - Social Science Division, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Colleges of the Capital District, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - College of Arts and Sciences- Deans' Bulletin, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Association of College Unions, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of NYS, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Academic Costumes, Designs- Correspondences, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Advisory Bd- Repoints, Resolutions, and Related Materials, 1953-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Advisory Board, 1954-1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Advisory Board, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Advisory Board- Budget Materials, 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - State College Athletic Advisory Board- Minutes, 1955-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - State College Athletic Advisory Board- Proposed Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Atmospheric Science Research Center, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Atmospheric Science Research Center, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Atmospheric Science Research Center, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Audio Visual Materials, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Audio Visual Aids, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Audio Visual Services (state college film services), 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - [NYSCT] Benevolent Association, 1951-1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Department of Biology, 1951-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Biology Department, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Biology Department, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bishop's Conferences, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - [B.E.] Blaisdell, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of SUNY Board of Trustees Meetings, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of SUNY Board of Trustees Meetings, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Board of Visitors, 1949-1953; 1955 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brubacher Hall, 1951 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brubacher Hall, 1951 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Brubacher Hall, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondences with George Brewer (faculty student association), 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Budget Information, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Budget Summary, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Budget Requests, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Budget Material, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Budget Material, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Budget- Balances by Months, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Budget Capital Construction, 1955-1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Budget Capital Construction, 1955-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Budget Capital Construction, 1955-1962 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Budget Requests- Equipment- Replacement and Additional, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Budget Requests- Equipment- Replacement and Additional, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Capital Construction Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - C, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - C, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Endowment, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 3)